■ brett.star7@outlook.com

Wroclaw, Poland

Profile

I am a senior web developer who specializes in SPA development using JavaScript. I'm especially expertized in React.js and Vue.js as well as having some experience with Angular. I also have rich experience in building backend APIs using Node.js and Python. I love learning and challenging.

Employment History

Senior Frontend Developer, Exclusive Networks France

April 2020 — July 2022

- Implemented optimization for high performance
- Developed many reusable components in React.js
- Developed frontend using SCSS and jQuery
- Unit and E2E tests using Jest and Cypress

Senior Full Stack Developer, Solid State PLC

February 2019 — January 2020

- Developed customer service platforms using React.js and Typescript
- Developed frontend pages using Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS
- Created reusable codes and styles
- Developed back-end APIs using Express and Django and integrated third-party APIs

Senior Frontend Developer, Softec S.p.A.

January 2018 — November 2018

- Developed many mobile apps using React Native
- Developed frontend using Material UI and React-Bootstrap
- Worked with Figma designs
- Took part in developing projects using Next.js and Rest APIs

Education

Bachelor of Science, Singapore University of Technology and Design

2013 — 2017

Skills
HTML/CSS/SCSS
Bootstrap 5/Tailwind CSS
React
React Native
JavaScript
Typescript
Vue
Angular
Node.js
Python
Django
Next.js
Nuxt.js
PHP
Laravel Framework
GraphQL
PostgreSQL
MongoDB
MySQL
Languages
English
Hobbies

Internet surfing, Listening to Music